Guide to the The New Leader Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VI: Photographs, 1906-2005, undated
  - Eshkol, Levi, 1958-1959 (Box 180, Folder 35)
  - Eskimos, undated (Box 180, Folder 36)
  - Essy, Amara, 1994 (Box 180, Folder 37)
  - Estensoro, Victor Paz, 1951-1971, undated (Box 180, Folder 38)
  - Ethiopia, 1949-1984, undated (Box 180, Folder 39)
  - Evanston Church Meeting, 1954 (Box 180, Folder 40)
  - Euratom-European Community, 1957, undated (Box 180, Folder 41)
  - Euro-Parliament--Strasbourg, 1979 (Box 180, Folder 42)
  - Evatt, Herbert, undated (Box 180, Folder 43)
  - Evers, Charles, 1968-1971, undated (Box 180, Folder 44)
  - Evers, Medgar, 1955-1963 (Box 180, Folder 45)
  - Mt. Everest Expeditions, 1931-1954, undated (Box 180, Folder 46)
  - Ewing, Oscar, undated (Box 180, Folder 47)
  - Eyskens, Gaston, 1953-1960 (Box 180, Folder 48)
  - Eytan, Gen. Rafael, 1978, undated (Box 180, Folder 49)
  - Fabius, Laurent, 1982-1984 (Box 180, Folder 50)
  - Fabre, Robert, undated (Box 180, Folder 51)
  - Fagerholm, Karl August, 1948, undated (Box 180, Folder 52)
  - Faik, Col. Abdul Kadir, 1958 (Box 180, Folder 53)
  - Fairchild, Thomas E., undated (Box 180, Folder 54)
  - Fairless, Benjamin F., 1942-1951 (Box 180, Folder 55)
  - Faisal, King, 1958-1973, undated (Box 180, Folder 56)
  - Falldin, Thorbjorn, 1976 (Box 180, Folder 57)
  - Falkland Islands, 1982 (Box 180, Folder 58)
  - Fanfani, Amintori, 1954-1974 (Box 180, Folder 59)
  - Faris, El-Khouri, undated (Box 180, Folder 60)
  - Farley, James A., 1951 (Box 180, Folder 61)
  - Farmer, James, 1964 (Box 180, Folder 62)
  - Farouk, King, 1950, undated (Box 180, Folder 63)
  - Faubus, Gov. Orval, 1957-1958 (Box 180, Folder 64)
  - Faulkner, Brian, 1971 (Box 180, Folder 65)
  - Faure, Edgar, 1952, undated (Box 180, Folder 66)
  - Fawzi, Mahmoud, 1970, undated (Box 180, Folder 67)
  - Fawzi, Mohammed, 1970 (Box 180, Folder 68)
  - Feather, Leonard, undated (Box 180, Folder 69)
  - Feldstein, Martin, 1983 (Box 180, Folder 70)
  - Ferguson, Homer, 1949, undated (Box 180, Folder 71)
  - Ferraro, Geraldine A., 1984 (Box 180, Folder 72)
  - Ferre, Luis A., 1963-1966 (Box 180, Folder 73)
  - Feynman, Richard, undated (Box 180, Folder 74)
  - Field, Frederick Vanderbilt, 1951 (Box 180, Folder 75)
  - Field, Winston--S. Rhodesia, 1960-1963 (Box 180, Folder 76)
  - Fields, Herman & Noel, 1954 (Box 180, Folder 77)
  - Figl, Leopold, undated (Box 180, Folder 78)
  - Figueiredo, Joao, 1981-1983 (Box 180, Folder 79)
  - Figueres, Jose, 1954, undated (Box 180, Folder 80)
  - Fine, John S., undated (Box 180, Folder 81)
  - Finletter, Thomas K., 1950-1952, undated (Box 180, Folder 82)
  - Firefighters, 1982 (Box 180, Folder 83)
  - Fischer, Louis, undated (Box 180, Folder 84)
  - Fischer, Ruth, 1947 (Box 180, Folder 85)
  - Fishbein, Dr. Morris, undated (Box 180, Folder 86)
  - Flanders, Sen., Ralph E., undated (Box 180, Folder 87)
  - Flanigan, Peter M., 1974 (Box 180, Folder 88)
  - Flowers, Richmond, 1965 (Box 180, Folder 89)
  - Flynn, John T., undated (Box 180, Folder 90)
  - Folsom, Gov. J., undated (Box 180, Folder 91)
  - Folsom, Marion B., 1955-1958 (Box 180, Folder 92)
  - Foot, Michael, 1976-1981, undated (Box 180, Folder 93)
  - Ford, Cong. Gerald, 1964-1979 (Box 180, Folder 94)
  - Ford, Henry, II, 1951-1971 (Box 180, Folder 95)
  - Ford, James W., 1936, undated (Box 180, Folder 96)
  - Forlani, Arnaldo, 1982 (Box 180, Folder 97)
  - Forman, James, 1969 (Box 180, Folder 98)
  - Forrestal, James T., 1948-1949 (Box 180, Folder 99)
  - Fortas, Abe, 1950 (Box 180, Folder 100)
  - Fortier, L. Yves, 1988-1991 (Box 180, Folder 101)
  - Foster, William T., 1948-1951, undated (Box 180, Folder 102)
  - Fowler, Henry, 1965-1966 (Box 180, Folder 103)
  - Fox, Vicente Quesada, undated (Box 180, Folder 104)
  - France--Personalities, 1947-1964, undated (Box 180, Folder 105)
  - France--Scenes, 1947-1980, undated (Box 180, Folder 106)
  - Franjieh, Suleiman, 1974-1976 (Box 180, Folder 107)
  - Frank, Anne, 1952-1957 (Box 180, Folder 108)
  - Frankfurter, Felix, 1954-1957, undated (Box 180, Folder 109)
  - Franco, Gen. Francisco, 1949-1968, undated (Box 180, Folder 110)
  - Fraser, Donald M., 1974 (Box 180, Folder 111)
  - Fraser, Douglas, 1981, undated (Box 180, Folder 112)
  - Fraser, Malcolm, 1975 (Box 180, Folder 113)
  - Frasyniuk, Wiadstaw, undated (Box 180, Folder 114)
  - Fredericks, Carlton, undated (Box 180, Folder 115)
  - Frechette, Louise, 1998 (Box 180, Folder 116)
  - Freedom Riders, 1961, undated (Box 180, Folder 117)
  - Freeman, Orville, 1958-1960, undated (Box 180, Folder 118)
  - Frei, Eduardo, 1950-1969, undated (Box 180, Folder 119)
  - French Commission--Austria Peace Treaty, 1947 (Box 180, Folder 120)
  - French West Africa--Scenes, 1940-1957, undated (Box 180, Folder 121)
  - Freud, Dr. Sigmund, 1936-1938 (Box 180, Folder 122)
  - Frey, Roger, 1961-1962 (Box 180, Folder 123)
  - Frichtman, Rev. Stephen, undated (Box 180, Folder 124)
  - Friedman, Milton, 1964-1968 (Box 180, Folder 125)
  - Frohmayer, John E., 1993 (Box 180, Folder 126)
  - Frondizi, Arturo, 1958 (Box 180, Folder 127)
  - Fry, Varian, 1940-1950 (Box 180, Folder 128)
  - Fuchs, Klaus, undated (Box 180, Folder 129)
  - Fujii, Hirohisha, 1994 (Box 180, Folder 130)
  - Fukuda, Takeo, 1971 (Box 180, Folder 131)
  - Fulbright, J.W., 1955-1969, undated (Box 180, Folder 132)
  - Fuller, Charles, undated (Box 180, Folder 133)
  - Furcolo, Foster, undated (Box 180, Folder 134)
  - Furtseva, undated (Box 180, Folder 135)
  - Fydrych, Waldemar, undated (Box 180, Folder 136)
  - Gaillard, Felix, 1957 (Box 180, Folder 137)
  - Gaitskell, Hugh, 1950-1989 (Box 180, Folder 138)
  - Galan, Luis Carlos, 1989 (Box 180, Folder 139)
  - Galanskov, undated (Box 180, Folder 140)
  - Galbraith, John K., 1961-1994, undated (Box 180, Folder 141)
  - Gallegos, Romulo, undated (Box 180, Folder 142)
  - Galindez, Jesus de--plus case photos, 1957-1958, undated (Box 180, Folder 143)
  - Gallup, George, undated (Box 180, Folder 144)
  - Gandhi, 1948, undated (Box 180, Folder 145)
  - Gandhi, Mrs. Indira, 1956-1981, undated (Box 180, Folder 146)
  - Gandhi, Rajiv, undated (Box 180, Folder 147)
  - Gandhi, Sanjay, 1977-1979 (Box 180, Folder 148)
  - Ganev, Stoyan, 1992 (Box 180, Folder 149)
  - Ganey, Judge J. Cullen, 1959 (Box 180, Folder 150)
  - Garba, Joseph N., 1990 (Box 180, Folder 151)
  - Gardiner, Robert, 1963 (Box 180, Folder 152)
  - Gardner, John W., 1966-1968 (Box 180, Folder 153)
  - Garelick, Sanford D., 1966 (Box 180, Folder 154)
  - Garfield, James, undated (Box 180, Folder 155)
  - Garment, Leonard, 1973, undated (Box 180, Folder 156)
  - Gates, John, undated (Box 180, Folder 157)
  - Gavin, James M., 1958-1967, undated (Box 180, Folder 158)
  - Gede, Tadeusz, undated (Box 180, Folder 159)
  - Geijer, Arne, undated (Box 180, Folder 160)
  - Gemayel, Amin, 1982 (Box 180, Folder 161)
  - Gemayel, Pierre, 1958, 1964 (Box 180, Folder 162)
  - Geneen, Harold S., 1972 (Box 180, Folder 163)
  - General Motors Strike, 1937 (Box 180, Folder 164)
  - Geneva Conference--Far East, 1954, undated (Box 180, Folder 165)
  - Geneva Conference--Big Four, 1955-1960, undated (Box 180, Folder 166)
  - Geneva Conon Laos, 1961 (Box 180, Folder 167)
  - Geneva Conference, 1962 (Box 180, Folder 168)
  - Georges-Picot, Guillame, 1951 (Box 180, Folder 169)
  - Gerhardsen, Einar, undated (Box 180, Folder 170)
  - Geremek, Bronislaw, undated (Box 180, Folder 171)
  - German Generals, 1945-1975, undated (Box 180, Folder 172)
  - German Housing, 1958-1992, undated (Box 180, Folder 173)
  - Germany--Scenes exc. Berlin, 1945-1993, undated (Box 180, Folder 174)
  - Gerstenmaier, Eugen, 1953-1956 (Box 180, Folder 175)
  - Ghana, 1951-1982 (Box 180, Folder 176)
  - Gheorghiu-Det, 1960, 1965 (Box 180, Folder 177)
  - Ghulam, Mohammed, 1951, 1953 (Box 180, Folder 178)
  - Giap, Vo Nguyen, 1966 (Box 180, Folder 179)
  - Gibbs, Humphrey, 1965 (Box 180, Folder 180)
  - Gibraltar, 1950 (Box 180, Folder 181)
  - Gideonse, Harry, undated (Box 180, Folder 182)
  - Gierek, Edward, 1974-1977, undated (Box 180, Folder 183)
  - Gil Robles, Jose, 1962 (Box 180, Folder 184)
  - Gilden, George, undated (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - Gillette, Sen. Guy, 1950, 1952, undated (Box 181, Folder 2)
  - Gilligan, John J., 1973 (Box 181, Folder 3)
  - Gilpatric, Roswell, 1960 (Box 181, Folder 4)
  - Ginsburg, 1968 (Box 181, Folder 5)
  - Ginzburg, Alexander--Russian, 1977, undated (Box 181, Folder 6)
  - Ginzburg, Irina, Ludmila, 1978 (Box 181, Folder 7)
  - Glemp, Jozef, 1981 (Box 181, Folder 8)
  - Glenn, John, 1983 (Box 181, Folder 9)
  - Glubb, Sir John Bagot, 1948-1956, undated (Box 181, Folder 10)
  - Gluck, Maxwell H., 1955, undated (Box 181, Folder 11)
  - Goddard, Terry, undated (Box 181, Folder 12)
  - Goetz, Bernhard, 1984, undated (Box 181, Folder 13)
  - Gold, 1937 (Box 181, Folder 14)
  - Gold, Harry, 1950, undated (Box 181, Folder 15)
  - Goldberg, Arthur, 1959-1965 (Box 181, Folder 16)
  - Goldberger, David, 1978 (Box 181, Folder 17)
  - Goldfine, Bernard, 1958, undated (Box 181, Folder 18)
  - Goldwater, Barry, 1952-1964 (Box 181, Folder 19)
  - Gomez, Laureano, 1949 (Box 181, Folder 20)
  - Gompers, Samuel, 1881-1924 (Box 181, Folder 21)
  - Gomulka, Wadislaw, 1957-1965, undated (Box 181, Folder 22)
  - Gonez, Arpad, undated (Box 181, Folder 23)
  - Gonzalez, Felipe, 1982 (Box 181, Folder 24)
  - Gonzalez, Henry B., 1957 (Box 181, Folder 25)
  - Gorbachev, Mikhail, 1988-1991 (Box 181, Folder 26)
  - Gorbachev, Raise, undated (Box 181, Folder 27)
  - Gordon, John F., 1958 (Box 181, Folder 28)
  - Gormley, Joe, 1978-1979 (Box 181, Folder 29)
  - Gottwald, Klement, 1951, undated (Box 181, Folder 30)
  - Goulart, Joao, 1962-1964 (Box 181, Folder 31)
  - Gowon, Yakubu, undated (Box 181, Folder 32)
  - Grady, Henry F., 1950 (Box 181, Folder 33)
  - Graham, Billy, 1954-1955 (Box 181, Folder 34)
  - Graham, Frank, 1950, undated (Box 181, Folder 35)
  - Granger, Lester B., undated (Box 181, Folder 36)
  - Grattan, C. Hartley, undated (Box 181, Folder 37)
  - Gray, Gordon, undated (Box 181, Folder 38)
  - Grayson, C. Jackson, 1971 (Box 181, Folder 39)
  - Grechko, Marshal Andrei, 1956-1957 (Box 181, Folder 40)
  - Greece, 1946, undated (Box 181, Folder 41)
  - Green, Edith, undated (Box 181, Folder 42)
  - Green, John, undated (Box 181, Folder 43)
  - Greenspan, Alan, 1974-1982 (Box 181, Folder 44)
  - Grenada, 1983 (Box 181, Folder 45)
  - Griffin, Gov. Marvin, 1955, undated (Box 181, Folder 46)
  - Griffin, Robert P., 1959-1970 (Box 181, Folder 47)
  - Griffin, William, undated (Box 181, Folder 48)
  - Griffin, Virgil, 1975 (Box 181, Folder 49)
  - Griffis, Stanton, 1950 (Box 181, Folder 50)
  - Griffith, Martha, undated (Box 181, Folder 51)
  - Griffiths, Martin, 1997 (Box 181, Folder 52)
  - Grigorenko, Piotr, 1968 (Box 181, Folder 53)
  - Grimes murder, 1957 (Box 181, Folder 54)
  - Grishin, Viktor V., 1971 (Box 181, Folder 55)
  - Grivas, Gen. George, 1959 (Box 181, Folder 56)
  - Gromyko, 1952-1977 (Box 181, Folder 57)
  - Gronchi, Giovanni, undated (Box 181, Folder 58)
  - Grotewohl, Otto, 1949, undated (Box 181, Folder 59)
  - Gruenther, Alfred M., 1953-1954, undated (Box 181, Folder 60)
  - Grundy, Joseph R., undated (Box 181, Folder 61)
  - Guatemala--Scenes and Personalities, 1942-1989, undated (Box 181, Folder 62)
  - Guevara, Major Ernesto "Che", 1960-1961 (Box 181, Folder 63)
  - Guinea--Scenes, 1958-1978, undated (Box 181, Folder 64)
  - Gulledge, Eugene, 1969 (Box 181, Folder 65)
  - Gur, Lt. Gen. Mordecha, 1978 (Israel) (Box 181, Folder 66)
  - Gurirab, Theo-Ben, undated (Box 181, Folder 67)
  - Guns, 1955-1975 (Box 181, Folder 68)
  - Gursel, Lt. Gen. Cemal, 1960 (Box 181, Folder 69)
  - Gyorkos, Istuan, undated (Box 181, Folder 70)
  - Guyana, 1940-1954 (Box 181, Folder 71)
  - Habash, George, 1969-1988 (Box 181, Folder 72)
  - Habib, Philip C., 1970, 1980 (Box 181, Folder 73)
  - Haddad, Saad, 1982, undated (Box 181, Folder 74)
  - Messali, Hadj, 1947, 1959 (Box 181, Folder 75)
  - Hagerty, James C., 1956 (Box 181, Folder 76)
  - Hahn, Emily, undated (Box 181, Folder 77)
  - Haig, Alexander, 1973-1986, undated (Box 181, Folder 78)
  - Hain, Peter, 1978 (Box 181, Folder 79)
  - Haiti, 1951-1963 (Box 181, Folder 80)
  - Hakata, 1946 (Box 181, Folder 81)
  - Haldeman, H.R., 1968 (Box 181, Folder 82)
  - Hall, Gov. Fred, undated (Box 181, Folder 83)
  - Hall, Leonard, undated (Box 181, Folder 84)
  - Hall, Paul, 1951-1962 (Box 181, Folder 85)
  - Halleck, Charles A., 1959 (Box 181, Folder 86)
  - Halley, Rudolph, 1951, undated (Box 181, Folder 87)
  - Hallgrimsson, Geir, 1978 (Box 181, Folder 88)
  - Halsey, Admiral Wm., undated (Box 181, Folder 89)
  - Hammarskjold, Dag, 1955-1961 (Box 181, Folder 90)
  - Hammer, Armand, undated (Box 181, Folder 91)
  - Hammid Seraj, Abdul, undated (Box 181, Folder 92)
  - Hand, Learned, 1958, 1961, undated (Box 181, Folder 93)
  - Hannay, David, 1990 (Box 181, Folder 94)
  - Hansonne, Michael, undated (Box 181, Folder 95)
  - Hari, Mata, undated (Box 181, Folder 96)
  - Harper, Judge Roy W., 1957 (Box 181, Folder 97)
  - Harlan, John Marshall, 1955, undated (Box 181, Folder 98)
  - Harriman, Averell, 1949-1968, undated (Box 181, Folder 99)
  - Harrington, Michael, undated (Box 181, Folder 100)
  - Harris, Ford, 1968, 1971, undated (Box 181, Folder 101)
  - Harris, Louis, undated (Box 181, Folder 102)
  - Harris, Oren, 1958, undated (Box 181, Folder 103)
  - Harris, Patricia, 1972, 1977 (Box 181, Folder 104)
  - Harris, Sam, undated (Box 181, Folder 105)
  - Harris, Seymour, undated (Box 181, Folder 106)
  - Harrison, George, undated (Box 181, Folder 107)
  - Harrison, Wm. Henry, 1950, undated (Box 181, Folder 108)
  - Harrison, William K., 1953 (Box 181, Folder 109)
  - Hart, Charles, undated (Box 181, Folder 110)
  - Hart, Gary, 1983-1991, undated (Box 181, Folder 111)
  - Hart, Merwin K., 1950 (Box 181, Folder 112)
  - Hartsfield, William B., 1953, undated (Box 181, Folder 113)
  - Harvard Disturbance, 1939-1969, undated (Box 181, Folder 114)
  - Hassan, King, 1960-1971 (Morocco) (Box 181, Folder 115)
  - Hassan, Moises, 1979 (Box 181, Folder 116)
  - Hatfield, Mark O., 1968-1971 (Box 181, Folder 117)
  - Hatoyama, Ichiro, 1954-1955, undated (Box 181, Folder 118)
  - Hatta, Mohammed, 1948-1950, undated (Box 181, Folder 119)
  - Hattersley, Roy, 1985 (Box 181, Folder 120)
  - Hauge, Dr. Gabriel, undated (Box 181, Folder 121)
  - Haughey, Charles, 1987 (Ireland) (Box 181, Folder 122)
  - Havel, Vaclav, undated (Box 181, Folder 123)
  - Hawke, Robert James Lee, 1983 (Box 181, Folder 124)
  - Hawkins, Rep. Augustus, 1975, 1977 (Box 181, Folder 125)
  - Hayden, Tom, 1968-1969, undated (Box 181, Folder 126)
  - Hays, Arthur Garfield, undated (Box 181, Folder 127)
  - Healey, Denis, 1970-1978, undated (Box 181, Folder 128)
  - Heath, Edward, 1965-1971, undated (Box 181, Folder 129)
  - Heaton, Maj. Gen. Leonard D., 1956 (Box 181, Folder 130)
  - Hebert, Edward, undated (Box 181, Folder 131)
  - Hedtoft, Hans, undated (Box 181, Folder 132)
  - Heinemann, Gustav, 1970 (Box 181, Folder 133)
  - Heinz, Sen. H. John, 1977 (Box 181, Folder 134)
  - Heller, Walter, 1970, undated (Box 181, Folder 135)
  - Henderson, Dr. Elmer L., undated (Box 181, Folder 136)
  - Henderson, Leon, 1947, undated (Box 181, Folder 137)
  - Henderson Strike, 1959, undated (North Carolina) (Box 181, Folder 138)
  - Hennings, Sen. Thomas C., 1956 (Box 181, Folder 139)
  - Herriot, Eduoard, 1942-1948, undated (Box 181, Folder 140)
  - Hershey, Gen. Louis B., 1965-1966 (Box 181, Folder 141)
  - Herter, Christian, 1959-1960 (Box 181, Folder 142)
  - Herzl, Dr. Theodore, undated (Box 181, Folder 143)
  - Herzog, Chaim, 1975-1978 (Box 181, Folder 144)
  - Heseltine, Michael, 1981 (Box 181, Folder 145)
  - Hesse, Horst, 1956 (Box 181, Folder 146)
  - Heuss, Theodor, 1945, 1949, undated (Box 181, Folder 147)
  - Heyns, Roger, 1965 (Box 181, Folder 148)
  - Hickel, Walter J., 1969-1970 (Box 181, Folder 149)
  - Hickenlooper, Bourke, 1962 (Box 181, Folder 150)
  - Hicks, Granville, undated (Box 181, Folder 151)
  - Hiestand, Rep. Edgar, 1961 (Box 181, Folder 152)
  - Hijackings--Terrorists, 1977 (Box 181, Folder 153)
  - Hildebrandt, Dr. Rainer, undated (Box 181, Folder 154)
  - Hill, Lister, undated (Box 181, Folder 155)
  - Hill, Robert C., 1954-1959 (Box 181, Folder 156)
  - Hillary, Sir Edmund, 1953-1954, undated (Box 181, Folder 157)
  - Hindenburg, Paul Von, 1932-1939 (Box 181, Folder 158)
  - Hinder, Rita, undated (Box 181, Folder 159)
  - Hinton, Deane, 1981 (Box 181, Folder 160)
  - Hirohito, 1955-1971 (Box 181, Folder 161)
  - Hiss, Alger and Priscilla, 1948-1951, undated (Box 181, Folder 162)
  - Hitler, 1933-1945, undated (Box 181, Folder 163)
  - Hoare, Sir Samuel, 1935, 1939 (Box 181, Folder 164)
  - Hobby, Oveta Culp, 1952-1953, undated (Box 181, Folder 165)
  - Ho Chi Minh, 1955-1965, undated (Box 181, Folder 166)
  - Hodge, Gen. John R., 1948 (Box 181, Folder 167)
  - Hodges, Luther, 1958, 1960 (Box 181, Folder 168)
  - Hoess, Rudolf, 1946, undated (Box 181, Folder 169)
  - Hoffa, James, 1957, undated (Box 181, Folder 170)
  - Hoffman, Paul, 1950, undated (Box 181, Folder 171)
  - Hoffman, Abbie, undated (Box 181, Folder 172)
  - Holifield, Chet, undated (Box 181, Folder 173)
  - Holkeri, Harri, undated (Box 181, Folder 174)
  - Hollai, Imre, 1982 (Box 181, Folder 175)
  - Holland, undated (Box 181, Folder 176)
  - Hollings, Ernest, 1982 (Box 181, Folder 177)
  - Holmes, John Haynes, undated (Box 181, Folder 178)
  - Home, Prime Minister, Britain, 1961-1963 (Box 181, Folder 179)
  - Honduras--Scenes, 1950-1969, undated (Box 181, Folder 180)
  - Honecker, Erich, 1981 (Box 181, Folder 181)
  - Hong Kong, 1954-1982, undated (Box 181, Folder 182)
  - Hook, Sidney, 1958, 1987, undated (Box 181, Folder 183)
  - Hooks, Benjamin, 1980-1982 (Box 181, Folder 184)
  - Hoopes, Townsend, 1964 (Box 181, Folder 185)
  - Hoover, Edgar, undated (Box 181, Folder 186)
  - Hoover, Herbert, 1949, undated (Box 181, Folder 187)
  - Horthy, Admiral, 1940, undated (Box 181, Folder 188)
  - Houdek, Vladimir, undated (Box 181, Folder 189)
  - Houphouet-Boigny, 1957-1983 (Box 181, Folder 190)
  - Hourany, Akran, 1957 (Box 181, Folder 191)
  - Housing, 1935-1969, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 181, Folder 192 to 193)
  - Hovde, Dr. Carl F., 1968 (Box 181, Folder 194)
  - Hoveida, Amir Abass, 1968 (Box 181, Folder 195)
  - Howard, Catherine G., 1953 (Box 181, Folder 196)
  - Hoxha, 1957, undated (Box 181, Folder 197)
  - Hua Kuo-feng, 1976-1978 (Box 181, Folder 198)
  - Huang Chen, 1977, undated (Box 181, Folder 199)
  - Huang Hua, 1978 (Box 181, Folder 200)
  - Huggins, Sir Godfrey, undated (Box 181, Folder 201)
  - Hughes, Charles Evans, 1941 (Box 181, Folder 202)
  - Hughes, Harold, undated (Box 181, Folder 203)
  - Hughes, Richard, 1964-1968 (Box 181, Folder 204)
  - Hughes, Sarah T., undated (Box 181, Folder 205)
  - Humphrey, Geo. M, 1955, undated (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H., 1959-1975, undated (Box 182, Folder 2)
  - Hungary--People and Personalities, 1948-1961, undated (Box 182, Folder 3)
  - Hungary--Scenes, 1947-1971, undated (Box 182, Folder 4)
  - Hunt, H.L., 1954 (Box 182, Folder 5)
  - Hurd, Douglas, 1981 (Box 182, Folder 6)
  - Hurley, Patrick, undated (Box 182, Folder 7)
  - Hurvitz, Yigal, undated (Box 182, Folder 8)
  - Husak, Gustav, 1968-1970 (Box 182, Folder 9)
  - Hu Shih, undated (Box 182, Folder 10)
  - Hussein, Lt. Col. Achmad, 1958 (Box 182, Folder 11)
  - Hussein, King, 1952-1995, undated (Box 182, Folder 12)
  - Hussein, Saddam, 2002 (Box 182, Folder 13)
  - Hutcheson, Bill, undated (Box 182, Folder 14)
  - Hutchins, Robt., undated (Box 182, Folder 15)
  - Huxley, Julian, 1957 (Box 182, Folder 16)
  - Hydra Island, undated (Box 182, Folder 17)
  - Hynes, John B., 1947-1955 (Box 182, Folder 18)
  - Ibanez, Carlos, 1952-1957, undated (Box 182, Folder 19)
  - Ibarruri, Dolores, 1976-1977 (La Pasionaria) (Box 182, Folder 20)
  - IBM, 2001 (Box 182, Folder 21)
  - Idris, 1958-1962 (King) (Box 182, Folder 22)
  - Ignatov, Maj. Gen. Nikolai, 1943, 1962 (Box 182, Folder 23)
  - Ikeda, Hatoyama, 1960-1961 (Box 182, Folder 24)
  - Ileto, Rafael, 1986 (Box 182, Folder 25)
  - ILGWU, 1948, undated (Box 182, Folder 26)
  - Illueca, Jorge E., 1983 (Box 182, Folder 27)
  - Immigration, undated (Box 182, Folder 28)
  - Impellitteri, 1953 (Box 182, Folder 29)
  - India, 1947-1984, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 182, Folder 30 to 31)
  - India--Industry--Farming--Housing, 1943-1977, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 182, Folder 32 to 33)
  - Indian Army, 1961, 1965, undated (combat scenes also) (Box 182, Folder 34)
  - Indian Culture, 1985 (Box 182, Folder 35)
  - Indians--American, 1952-1974, undated (Box 182, Folder 36)
  - Indo-China--Refugees, 1979, undated (Box 182, Folder 37)
  - Indo-China War, 1947-1954, undated (See also: Vietnam War) (Box 182, Folder 38)
  - Indonesia, 1941-1971, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 182, Folder 39 to 40)
  - Ingrao, Pietro, undated (Box 182, Folder 41)
  - Inonu, Ismet, 1946-1957 (Box 182, Folder 42)
  - Isnanally, S. Rudolph, 1993 (Box 182, Folder 43)
  - International Atomic Energy Agency, 1954, 1957, undated (Box 182, Folder 44)
  - International Labor Organization, 1957, undated (Box 182, Folder 45)
  - International Monetary Fund, 1972 (Box 182, Folder 46)
  - Iran--Scenes, 1938-1988, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 182, Folder 47 to 48)
  - Iran-Iraq War, 1984 (Box 182, Folder 49)
  - Iraq, 1946-1985, undated (Box 182, Folder 50)
  - Ireland--Ulster unrest, 1969-1977 (Box 182, Folder 51)
  - Iribarne, Manuel Fraga, 1964 (Box 182, Folder 52)
  - Ioho, Isaac, undated (Box 182, Folder 53)
  - Ishibashi, Tanzah, undated (Box 182, Folder 54)
  - Ismay, Lord, 1952, undated (Box 182, Folder 55)
  - Israel--Buildings, 1946-1977, undated (Box 182, Folder 56)
  - Israel--People, 1948-1973 (Box 182, Folder 57)
  - Israel--Scenes, 1938-1990, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 182, Folder 58 to 59)
  - Israel--Terrorist Raid, 1978 (Box 182, Folder 60)
  - Israeli-Egyptian Peace Talks, 1972 (Box 182, Folder 61)
  - Israel--1973 War, 1967-1973 (Box 182, Folder 62)
  - Israeli War, 1967 (Box 182, Folder 63)
  - Instanbul, undated (Box 182, Folder 64)
  - Italy--Scenes, 1949-1975, undated (Box 182, Folder 65)
  - Ithaca Youth Assembly, 1951 (Box 182, Folder 66)
  - Ito, Ritsu, undated (Box 182, Folder 67)
  - Ives, Irving, undated (Box 182, Folder 68)
  - Iyad, Abu, 1986 (Box 182, Folder 69)
  - Ivory Coast, 1972, 1981 (Box 182, Folder 70)
  - Izetbegovic, Alija, 1995 (Box 182, Folder 71)
  - Jackson, C.D., undated (Box 182, Folder 72)
  - Jackson, Geoffrey, 1971 (Box 182, Folder 73)
  - Jackson, Henry M., 1949-1974, undated (Box 182, Folder 74)
  - Jackson, Rev. Jesse, 1971, 1978-1979 (Box 182, Folder 75)
  - Jacobsen, David, 1991 (Box 182, Folder 76)
  - Jaffe, Philip, 1950, undated (Box 182, Folder 77)
  - Jagan, Cheddi, 1953-1961, undated (Box 182, Folder 78)
  - Jagne, Baboucarr-Blaise I., 1999 (Box 182, Folder 79)
  - Jamaica, 1953-1978, undated (Box 182, Folder 80)
  - James, Hibbard G., undated (Box 182, Folder 81)
  - Jankowski, undated (Box 182, Folder 82)
  - Japan, Demonstrations, 1957-1962, undated (Box 182, Folder 83)
  - Japan--Scenes, 1936-1988, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 182, Folder 84 to 85)
  - Japanese-Americans, undated (Box 182, Folder 86)
  - Jarvis, Howard, 1978-1979 (Box 182, Folder 87)
  - Japanese Communists, 1949-1950 (Box 182, Folder 88)
  - Japanese Industry, 1965-1982, undated (Box 182, Folder 89)
  - Japanese Military, 1938-1961, undated (Box 182, Folder 90)
  - Japanese Relocation, undated (Box 182, Folder 91)
  - Jaroszewicz, Piotr, 1978 (Box 182, Folder 92)
  - Jarring, Gunar, 1957-1967, undated (Box 182, Folder 93)